MUHAMMAD AFIF

FRONT END DEVELOPER





1 081321972065



hammadaf9408@gmail.com



Super puma raya 9, Cimahi Selatan



mhdafif.vercel.app linkedin.com/in/mhdafif github.com/mhdafif

PROFILE

I'm an engineer who specializes in front end web applications. I can provide clean code and responsive for desktop and mobile. I also make website more interactive with animations. I'm interested in React and Vue but possible to adapt with a new technology

SKILLS

- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- HTML & CSS
- React
- Vue
- Node
- Redux
- Vuex
- Git
- Jest
- Testing Library

EXPERIENCE

FRONT END DEVELOPER - ULTRA VOUCHER

Jan 2022 - Present

- Developed and implemented software solutions based on client requirements
- Developed and implemented design UI/X from figma to our application
- Design unit testing for the components

FRONT END DEVELOPER - PROSPACE

Oct 2020 - Dec 2021

- Designs and creates software solutions to solve pain points for various
- Developed and implemented software solutions based on client requirements and feedback
- Tested and refined software prior to roll out
- Design unit testing for the components
- In charge of release the application to production
- Create UI Framework

FRONT END DEVELOPER - XSIS MITRA UTAMA

Sept 2018 - Sept 2020

- Re build Employee Self Service Application from web form to micro service with React Typescript
- Maintenance Employee Self Service Application
- Fixing bug in existing Employee Self Service website

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF INFORMATICS ENGINEERING

Telkom University

Aug 2012 - Jan 2018